var data = [
    {
        "Question": "Which is not a type of prototyping?",
        "A": "Wizard of Oz",
        "B": "Paper",
        "C": "Documentation",
        "D": "Mockup",
        "Answer": "Documentation"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is not a key design issue?",
        "A": "Distribution",
        "B": "Error handling",
        "C": "Interface",
        "D": "Persistence of Data",
        "Answer": "Interface"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is not a design process?",
        "A": "Interface design",
        "B": "Algorithm design",
        "C": "Data design",
        "D": "Integration design",
        "Answer": "Integration Design"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Iterative process through which requirements are translated into a “blueprint” for building software.",
        "A": "Architectural design",
        "B": "Component design",
        "C": "Software design",
        "D": "Interface design",
        "Answer": "Software Design"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Establishes a basic structural framework that identifies the major components of system and the communication among these components.",
        "A": "Architectural design",
        "B": "Component design",
        "C": "Software design",
        "D": "Interface design",
        "Answer": "Architectural Design"
    },
    {
        "Question": "A component reads streams of data on its inputs and produces streams of data on its outputs, delivering a complete instance of the result in a standard order.",
        "A": "Layered",
        "B": "Repository",
        "C": "Pipe and filter",
        "D": "Blackboard",
        "Answer": "Pipe and filter"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Consists of a central data store and a set of independent components that access the data store.",
        "A": "Layered",
        "B": "Repository",
        "C": "Pipe and filter",
        "D": "Blackboard",
        "Answer": "Repository"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Organizes a system into layers, each of which provide a set of services.",
        "A": "Layered",
        "B": "Repository",
        "C": "Pipe and filter",
        "D": "Blackboard",
        "Answer": "Layered"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Technique of linking two or more computers into a network (usually via a LAN) in order to take advantage of the parallel processing power of those computers.",
        "A": "Cloud computing",
        "B": "Grid computing",
        "C": "Cluster computing",
        "D": "Peer-to-peer",
        "Answer": "Cluster computing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Makes applications easily adapt to changing technologies and integrate with other applications.",
        "A": "CORBA",
        "B": "RPC",
        "C": "SOA",
        "D": "REST",
        "Answer": "SOA"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Describes how the software communicates within itself, to systems that interact with it, and with humans who use it.",
        "A": "Interface design",
        "B": "Data design",
        "C": "Algorithm design",
        "D": "Architectural design",
        "Answer": "Interface design"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is not a type of GoF Pattern?",
        "A": "Behvairal Patterns",
        "B": "Structural Patterns",
        "C": "Functional Patterns",
        "D": "Creational Patterns",
        "Answer": "Functional Patterns"
    }
];
